♪♪
EMBER
Meet the residents of Element City.
Air... usually has their
head in the clouds.
AIR PERSON
Aww, my new jacket!
EMBER
Earth... can be a little seedy.
EARTH PERSON
Nothing weird going on here.
Uh, just a little pruning!
EMBER
Water... is always getting into something.
YOUNG WADE
Oh... Huh...
[Screams]
YOUNG WADE
Help!
EMBER
And fire...
As ordered!
EMBER
We run a little hot.
[Burps]
BERNIE
This shop is dream of our family.
Someday it'll all be yours!
EMBER
But we all live by one simple rule.
CINDER
Elements cannot mix!
WADE
[Screams]
EMBER
What the...
WADE
The pipe squished me all out of shape.
EMBER
Dang!
WADE
That's better.
EMBER
Oh.
WADE
So you've never left Fire Town?
EMBER
Sorry, buddy. Elements don't mix.
EARTH PERSON
Hey!
EMBER
Plus, my dad would boil you alive.
WADE
Why does anyone get to tell you
what you can do in your life?
WADE
Come on!
Why do they even have these?
EMBER
Eh, who knows.
WADE
Watch this!
♪♪
EMBER
Whoa!
BERNIE
Ember, I see a change in you.
WADE
[Screaming]
CINDER
Water guy?
EMBER
You live here?
WADE
It's my mom's place.
ALAN
We got two kids that are
swimming around here somewhere.
ALAN
Marco! Polo!
MARCO
What? [Laughing]
EMBER
I've been trying to fill my father's shoes
but I never once asked
what I wanted to do.
♪♪
BERNIE
Try this!
EMBER
Dad, those are too hot.
WADE
I love hot food.
[Gulps]
WADE
[Screaming]
[Muffled screaming]
WADE
[Screaming]
EMBER
You see? He likes it!