Oh, my God!
Hang on!
- Ethan!
- Go, go, go!
Audiences and critics can't believe
what they're seeing.
Listen to me.
The world's coming after you.
Stay out of my way.
“Tom Cruise has outdone himself.”
With a 99% on Rotten Tomatoes.
Yes!
“Mission: Impossible - Dead Reckoning is filled with ‘holy shit’ moments.”
What is happening?
“This is why we go to the movies.”
Oh, I like her.
“It's pulse pounding.”
“It will rock your world.”
With “jaw dropping action.”
Is this where we run?
Go, go, go, go!
Probably.
“It's one of the best action movies
ever made.”
What more can I say?
“See it in the biggest, most seat-shaking theater you can find.”
“It will take your breath away.”
Ethan, did you make it?
Are you okay?